lotusleggings.com 2018-11-24

# Privacy Policy – Lotus Leggings

Your information’s security is taken very seriously. We have implemented procedures designed to safeguard your information and privacy in our policies. In order to protect your personal data from unauthorized access and use, we utilize computer safeguard security measures (firewalls, SSL, and secure passwords) in addition to our secure server. 

**What data is collected?**

We collect only the data you provide to us through our website, email/contact form, phone contact, and any other means of communication that you might use. By viewing our site, you agree to the collection and use of your information. If we believe it to be necessary to release your information to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect the rights of others, ourselves, property, or safety, we reserve the right to do so. Information that doesn’t personally identify our visitors may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or related uses.

We will not use your personal identifiable information for sell, trade, or transfer. This doesn’t include third parties that we trust to keep your information confidential who in some way assist us in operating our site, conducting our business, or servicing our customers, so long as those parties agree to comply with our policies. As you browse Lotus Leggings, advertising cookies may be placed in your computer so that we can better understand our customers’ interests and needs in order to provide better products and shopping experiences.

**Children and Minors:**

Our website and all products are directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.  We don't collect any information from minors under the age of 18 years of age. 

**What Happens When We Change Our Privacy Policy?**

By using this site, you are agreeing to and accepting the terms laid out in this Privacy Policy.  Lotus reserves the right to update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time if our practices change or are updated. If Lotus decides to make such changes to this Privacy Policy, an easily identifiable notice will be posted on the web site and/or sent to you via email, so that you will know the information that Lotus collects, how it uses that information, and the parties with whom it may share that information.
